A one-of-a-kind story about two-of-a-kind men who (for
better or worse) changed film forever
Electric Boogaloo: The Wild, Untold Story of Cannon Films is
a documentary film directed by Mark Hartley.
A documentary about the rise and fall of the Cannon Film Group, the legendary independent
film company helmed by Israeli cousins Menahem Golan and Yoram Globus.
Self - Actress, played by Molly Ringwald.
Self - Actor, played by Dolph Lundgren.
Self - Producer & Actress, played by Bo Derek.
Self - Actor, played by Alex Winter.
Self - Actor, played by Richard Chamberlain.
Self - Actress, played by Marina Sirtis.
Electric Boogaloo: The Wild, Untold Story of Cannon Films is a 2014
Australian-American documentary film written and directed by Mark Hartley.
It tells the story of cousins Menahem Golan and Yoram
Globus who headed The Cannon Group.
Those interviewed lay tribute to the brash, unconventional immigrant filmmakers who gave young actors a chance
and give unflinching anecdotes of both the hits and the low budget and often crass films created.
The film explores themes of movie business, show
business, rise and fall, b movie, hollywood.